https://www.adoptionstogether.org/privacy-policy/

Menu
Adoptions Together
Pregnant?En EspañolSpeak to a CounselorYour Pregnancy OptionsOpen AdoptionYour RightsFAQMeet Our Waiting FamiliesThe Adoption ProcessDo I Have to Tell the Father?Can You Put a Baby Up for Adoption After Birth?Why Do Women Decide to Give a Baby Up for Adoption?Giving Up a Baby for Adoption? Watch Out for These Red FlagsCan I Place My Baby for Adoption if I am Pregnant and Addicted?Compensation & Adoption Today10 Important Rights You Have When Giving Up a Baby for AdoptionGiving Up a Baby for Adoption and Positive Adoption LanguageBirth Parent BlogAdoptingInformation PacketsAdoption ApplicationAdopt an InfantWhat Kind of Adoption is Right for Me?What is Domestic Adoption?How Does Infant Adoption Work?How Much Does it Cost to Adopt?Legal Questions About AdoptionDomestic Infant Adoption PreparationAdopt from Foster CareHeart GalleryThe Foster Care Adoption ProcessThe Cost of Adopting from Foster CareAdopting from Foster CareFAQFamily Find Step Down ProjectHome StudyWhat is a Home Study?How Long does a home study take?How Much Does a Home Study Cost?What Information is Included in a Home Study?International Adoption Home StudiesHome Study ServicesHome Study ProcessHome Study FAQHome Study Service FeesApplicationInternational AdoptionSingle Parent AdoptionLGBT AdoptionPost-Adoption ServicesFamilyWorks TogetherFor Families: Counseling and TrainingFor ProfessionalsAbout UsAnnual ReportOur TeamBoard of DirectorsCareersInternshipsAccreditationsEventsTaste in PotomacDonateWays to SupportMonthly GivingPlanned GivingSponsor an Event with Adoptions Together2020 Virtual Taste in PotomacEventsHeart GalleryInformation PacketsContact UsCareersInternshipsNon-Discrimination and Privacy Policy
Adoptions Together
Social MediaRegisterWatch Taste in Potomac HereNon-Discrimination and Privacy PolicyAdoptions Together does not discriminate in employment practices or service delivery on the basis of race, color, national origin, religion, gender, age, disability, citizenship, marital status, creed, sexual orientation, gender expression or gender identity.Adoptions Together, Inc. recognizes and respects how important personal privacy is to you. Your personal information is the information specific to you that you provide us. This includes the information you share with us, whether in person or electronically.Here are the questions that we’re most often asked about privacy. If you don’t see your question on the list, please call us at 301-439-2900 or email us at info@adoptionstogether.org.When and why does Adoptions Together collect personal information?When you request services from us, we collect personal information in order to process your request. We keep this information as required by child placement agency laws and licensing regulations so that we can give you the services you request. Some of this information also goes to our bank, credit card and electronic check processors.
These companies follow the same security guidelines that we do.When you send us e-mail, we’ll keep the content of the e-mail, your e-mail address, and our response so that we can follow-up on questions you may have.How does Adoptions Together use the personal information I provide? Care is taken with the information you have provided to us because it represents the trust you place in us. Adoptions Together will use your personal information in the normal course of doing business simply to do what you’ve asked us to do. We will also use this information to provide positive identification of you when you contact us.Does Adoptions Together provide personal information to external parties? With the very narrow exceptions noted here, Adoptions Together does not and will not provide personal information to third parties without your permission. Under no circumstances will we sell your personal information to third parties.We may share personal information with business partners if they need that to give you the service you requested. For example, in order to process your credit card / debit card / checks, we give our partner only the information they need to provide this service.Your information may be disclosed to government authorities or other third parties when required by law, including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas, to report suspected child abuse or neglect, if we believe you pose a danger to yourself or others, or if a public health emergency exists.Do you track information related to my visits to your website? Your visit to our website is tracked through a standard web traffic statistics program, which keeps records of traffic on the site. Our server automatically collects data about your server’s Internet address when you visit us.
When you request pages from our website, our servers may log your IP address.Will I ever receive unsolicited mail from Adoptions Together? We do on occasion distribute information that may be of interest to our clients and community. Most frequently this takes the form of e-newsletters. If you would prefer not to receive communications from us, please let us know by calling 301-439-2900 or sending an email to info@adoptionstogether.org.Do I have any special rights because of federal laws or regulations? In addition to the rights described here, federal regulations (45 CFR 164) give you the right to:Request restrictions on certain uses and disclosures, although Adoptions Together is not required to agree to a requested restriction,Receive confidential communications of protected health information,Inspect and copy protected health information,Amend protected health information,Receive an accounting of disclosures, andObtain a paper copy of this Notice upon request.What should I do if I believe my privacy rights have been violated? Please contact us right away if you have reason to believe that Adoptions Together has violated your privacy rights.
You can email us at info@adoptionstogether.org, or call us at 301-439-2900.
In addition, you can file a complaint through our complaint procedures or with the U.S. Secretary of Health and Human Services.
Filing a complaint will not result in any action being taken against you. Remarketing Tag
